<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>全自动万能制造机 FullyAutomaticOmniCrafter</name>
    <author>Jeremie</author>
    <supportedVersions>
		<li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Jeremie.Fully.Automatic.OmniCrafter</packageId>
    <description>
[h2] 全自动万能制造机 FullyAutomaticOmniCrafter [/h2]

无中生有！将能量转化为物质！
全自动万能制造机 FullyAutomaticOmniCrafter 闪亮登场！
超凡世界的科技结晶，能将能量转化为物质，满足你对资源的无限需求！
无论是食物、药品还是建筑和材料，这台神奇的机器都能轻松制造出来！让你的殖民地焕发新生，迎接崭新的明天！
超凡科技！小子！



自带一个无限容量电池，可以存储无限多的电能。解决在制造超贵物品时需要制造大量电池的问题。

在制造物品时，首先消耗内置电池的电量，再消耗电网电池的电量。
但是！如果电网的供电能力超过了制造物品所需的能量，那么，不需要消耗任何存储的电能就能直接制造物品。没想到吧~！

一般情况下像正常电池一样工作，可以存储电网的电量，也可以在电网电量不足时释放电能。
如果不需要内置电池功能，只需要点击按钮关闭建筑的电源(按V)即可。

雨淋不会短路，电路短路不会爆炸（暂未测试）

另外，收藏夹会在存档间同步。

现在需要依赖Harmony的拦截功能来实现电力相关的内容。

[hr][/hr]

[h2] 物质-能量转化仪 MatterEnergyConverter [/h2]

将物质分解成夸克粒子，转化为弦场，随后将其抽取为能量！资源回收好帮手！
物质能量转化仪 MatterEnergyConverter 堂堂登场！

超凡世界的又一科技结晶，能将物质分解成夸克粒子，转化为弦场，随后将其抽取为能量！
无论是食物、药品还是建筑和材料，这台神奇的机器都能轻松分解！殖民地再也不会缺乏能源！
超凡科技说，要有光！

[h3] 有三种回收方法 [/h3]
[list]
 [*] 设置存储区设置，像存储建筑一样小人会自动搬运进去，再点转化存储物按钮，建筑上的所有物品就会被分解转化了。
 [*] 用空投仓的装载按钮像装载空投仓那样装载物品，再点转化装载物按钮，货舱里的物品就会被分解转化了。
 [*] 直接点定点转化按钮，随后用十字光标点需要转化的物品或建筑，就会立即被分解转化了。
[/list]

提示：物质能量转化仪的存储区不会老化、腐烂度会不断重置，因此可以作为特殊仓库暂存物品。

[hr][/hr]

[h3]建议配合使用的mod[/h3]

[list]
 [*] MinifyEverything 让所有建筑都支持打包（支持打包的建筑才能被成功生产出来） https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=872762753
[/list]

[hr][/hr]

可在Mod设置中调整能量转化公式。
Y = a + b·X + c·X² + d·X³ + e·X⁴ + g·log₁₀(X) + n·ln(X)
X = 物品的市场价值 + [ 物品重量 ] + [ 物品耐久 ]
能量 = Y [ * 品质乘数 ] * 数量
品质乘数：极差=0.5, 较差=0.8, 一般=1.0, 良好=2.0, 极佳=4.0, 大师=8.0, 传奇=16.0
默认 b=1，其他系数为0，即默认能量转化公式为 Y=X，线性关系。



[hr][/hr]

Source Code : https://github.com/Lyoko-Jeremie/RimworldMods/tree/master/FullyAutomaticOmniCrafter

---

[h2] Fully Automatic OmniCrafter [/h2]

Get Anything From Nothing! Convert energy into matter, meet your resource needs! 
Fully Automatic OmniCrafter is here! 
The technological gem of the archotech world, capable of converting energy into matter, satisfying your infinite resource demands!
Whether it's food, medicine, buildings, or materials, this magical machine can easily manufacture them all! Let your colony shine anew, ushering in a new era!
Archotech technology! Boys!


Comes with an infinite capacity battery that can store unlimited energy. Solves the problem of needing to manufacture a large number of batteries when crafting expensive items.

When crafting items, it first consumes the energy from the built-in battery, then consumes energy from the grid batteries.
BUT ! If the grid's power supply exceeds the energy required to craft the item, then you can craft the item directly without consuming any stored energy. Surprised, aren't you~!

Under normal circumstances, it works like a regular battery, storing energy from the grid and releasing energy when the grid's supply is insufficient.
If you don't need the built-in battery functionality, simply click the button to turn off the building's power (press V).

Rain won't cause short circuits, and electrical short circuits won't cause explosions (not yet tested).

Additionally, the favorites will sync across saves.

Now relies on Harmony's interception capabilities to implement power-related features.
		
[hr][/hr]

[h2] Matter-Energy Converter [/h2]

Decompose matter into quark particles, convert them into string fields, and then extract them as energy! A great helper for resource recycling!
The Matter-Energy Converter is here!

Another technological gem of the archotech world, capable of decomposing matter into quark particles, converting them into string fields, and then extracting them as energy!
Whether it's food, medicine, buildings, or materials, this magical machine can easily decompose them all! Your colony will never lack energy again!
Archotech technology says, let there be light!

[h3] Three conversion methods [/h3]
[list]
 [*] Set up a storage area, and colonists will automatically haul items onto it. Then click the "Convert Stored Items" button, and all items on the building will be decomposed and converted.
 [*] Use the loading button of the drop pod to load items as if loading a drop pod, then click the "Convert Loaded Items" button, and the items in the cargo hold will be decomposed and converted.
 [*] Directly click the "Targeted Conversion" button, then use the crosshair cursor to click on any target on the map that you want to convert, and it will be immediately decomposed and converted.
[/list]

Note: The storage area of the Matter-Energy Converter does not age, and the rot will constantly reset, so it can be used as a special warehouse for temporarily storing items.

[hr][/hr]

[h3]Recommended mods to use with Fully Automatic OmniCrafter[/h3]

[list]
[*] MinifyEverything Allows all buildings to be minified (only buildings that can be minified can be successfully produced) https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=872762753
[/list]

[hr][/hr]

You can adjust the energy conversion formula in the mod settings.
Y = a + b·X + c·X² + d·X³ + e·X⁴ + g·log₁₀(X) + n·ln(X)
X = Market Value of the item + [ Weight of the item ] + [ Durability of the item ]
Energy = Y [ * Quality Multiplier ] * Quantity
Quality Multiplier: Awful=0.5, Poor=0.8, Normal=1.0, Good=2.0, Excellent=4.0, Masterwork=8.0, Legendary=16.0
By default, b=1 and other coefficients are 0, so the default energy conversion formula is Y=X, a linear relationship.


[hr][/hr]

Source Code : https://github.com/Lyoko-Jeremie/RimworldMods/tree/master/FullyAutomaticOmniCrafter

	</description>
	<loadBefore>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
	</loadAfter>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
