<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>Jeremie 的 SNS:AOPC:TPOC 补丁</name>
    <author>Jeremie</author>
    <supportedVersions>
		<li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Jeremie.SNS.AOPC.TPOC.Patch</packageId>
    <description>
Jeremie 的 SNS:AOPC:TPOC 补丁 ， 在正义的基础上更进一步 ！

SNS : 科学永不止步 （Science Never Stops）
AOPC : 宇宙雄心 （Ambition of the Cosmic [Continued]）
TPOC : 真·创造巅峰 （AOTC: True Pinnacle of Creation[Continued]）

- 将 Ambition of the Cosmic: Custom Edition 中的 “时空立场投射仪(Temporal Barrier Projector)” ，并大幅增强了相关属性。
	由于时空立场投射仪是一个眼部饰品，这就意味着不需要干扰穿着的衣服，
	所以鼠鼠等具有特色服饰的种族可在保留服饰的基础上，通过这个物品获得各项属性加成和一个超级强力的随身能量护盾。
	此物品大幅增加了角色的搬运能力，工作速度，移动速度，战斗能力，生存能力。
	在安装 Animal Apparel: Framework (AnimalApparelFramework) 后，你的宠物也可以装备这个物品，获得同样的属性加成和护盾。
	在安装 边缘仙路 (RimImmortal) 后，能增加负重上限。
	在安装 奥德赛 DLC (Odyssey) 后，能增加真空抗性。
	在安装 AutoBlink 后，在穿戴时自动获得一个传送能力HeDiff "时空立场闪烁" 。如果存档中角色已经穿戴了这个物品，脱下再穿上即可获得传送能力。
	
	最适合的场景：
	- 鼠鼠、龙、猫猫等具有特色服饰的种族，想要在不牺牲外观的前提下获得强力属性加成和护盾。
	- 想要一个强力的终极防御装备选项的玩家。
	- 需要大量搬运能力的玩家。（例如使用 边缘弹道导弹 (IRBM) 但是觉得装填速度太慢）
	- 需要超模防御力的玩家。（穿上这个可以跟虫贴脸）

- 修改了 “稳定壁垒(Bastion of Stability)” 和 “永续自律型群星之怒炮塔(Eternal EXARCH Turret)” 的攻击准确度，使得其更加符合最强远程炮台的设定了。（再也不会人体描边乱炸一通，敌人衣角微脏，家里建筑却炸了个稀巴烂）
- 修改了 “星河水栽培III代(Cosmic Hydroponics Generation Omega)” 的肥沃度为 10000 ， 让它更符合最强水栽培的设定。解决了种植超级作物（生长时间600天的植物）的问题。（种植超级作物再也不需要依赖 永恒科学(Eternal Science) 的 生态方舱(Eco-Ark[EcoArk_LostS1ght]) 了）

- 时空立场投射仪 添加 CE 支持，虽然我不玩 CE ，但是也让 gemini 帮我写了 CE 补丁，如果有问题请及时反馈。
- 另外， AOTC 的 稳定壁垒 听说好像在CE中不工作。

- 修改 “奇迹垃圾分解器(Miraculous Wastepack Atomizer)” 的分解速度，虽然它的分解速度已经很快了，但我觉得它还可以再快一点点，所以就把它的分解速度提升了十倍。
- 修改 “稳定物质基因处理器(Stable Matter Gene Processor)” ，将容量调到10000，提供的基因复杂度调整为100000，让它更符合最强基因处理器的设定。

- 新增自动水栽培功能，现在为星河水栽培III代添加了自动采摘种植逻辑，只需要通电并选择植物类型，就可以自动种植了。
- 对于拥有大量水栽培盆的殖民地，这个特性可以大大减少管理水栽培盆所需的工作量和殖民者，减少Pawn太多导致的性能问题。
- 建议将水栽培盆设置为禁用，以免殖民者抢种植任务。 ~如果需要停止自动生长逻辑，直接断电即可。~
- 性能：在我681个mod的环境下，260个水栽培盆，TPS下降不明显。且因为效率远高于人工种植，目测实际上50个水培盆的效率几乎相当于200个水栽培盆的人工种植效率了。且水培盆本身效率越高，相对于人工种植的效率提升越大。
- 添加自动种植和自动收获开关，可以让玩家根据需要选择是否启用自动水栽培功能。

- 自动水栽培功能 已单独提取为独立Mod，移动到了 全自动水栽培盆 (FullyAutomaticHydroponics) (Jeremie.Fully.Automatic.Hydroponics) Mod 中。 https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3709212752

- 2026.03.20
- 再次增加了时空立场投射仪的携带能力，因为我发现外出时携带能力还不够大。

- 2026.03.22
- 为动物提供了穿戴时空立场投射仪的支持。现在动物也可以穿戴时空立场投射仪了。当风雪遗孤剧本下只有单主角与动物时，大大提升动物的存货率。
（需要安装能让动物穿衣服的mod框架：（Animal Apparel: Framework）） https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=3513825850

- 2026.03.23
- 让「隔岸观火」和「世界尽头」可以与盾牌一起装备。（貌似还存在问题？）（当使用了 Vanilla Weapons Expanded 的情况下） https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013

- 2026.04.16
- 添加 "时空立场闪烁" Hediff ， 修改中文名称为 "时空立场投射仪" 以便更符合语境。
- 修改了时空立场投射仪的价值，为了避免价值过高导致殖民地财富爆炸问题，现在价值是1，并且禁止自然生成在袭击者身上（应该），且星际贸易只会回收而不会销售它。现在应该只能通过乌托邦装置和开发者模式来获得。

- 2026.04.17
- 新增自动水栽培功能，现在为星河水栽培III代添加了自动采摘种植逻辑，只需要通电并选择植物类型，就可以自动种植了。

- 2026.04.17
- 自动采摘种植功能添加开关，可以让玩家根据需要选择是否启用自动水栽培功能。

- 2026.04.18
- 自动水栽培功能 已单独提取为独立Mod，移动到了 全自动水栽培盆 (FullyAutomaticHydroponics) (Jeremie.Fully.Automatic.Hydroponics) Mod 中。

Source Code: https://github.com/Lyoko-Jeremie/RimworldMods/tree/master/SNS_AOPC_TPOC_Patch

----------------

[The English Describe Translated by Gemini]


Jeremie's SNS:AOPC:TPOC Patch – Taking Justice One Step Further!

SNS: Science Never Stops
AOPC: Ambition of the Cosmic [Continued]
TPOC: True Pinnacle of Creation [Continued]


- Restored the "Temporal Barrier Projector" from Ambition of the Cosmic: Custom Edition and significantly buffed its attributes.
Since the projector is an eye accessory, it does not interfere with worn apparel.
This allows races with unique outfits (like Ratkins) to keep their signature look while gaining massive stat boosts and a super-powerful portable energy shield.
This item greatly enhances carrying capacity, work speed, movement speed, combat ability, and survivability.
With the Animal Apparel: Framework installed, your pets can also equip this item to gain the same stat boosts and shield.
With RimImmortal installed, it increases carrying capacity. With the Odyssey DLC installed, it increases vacuum resistance.
With Odyssey DLC installed, it increases vacuum resistance.
With AutoBlink installed, it grants an automatic teleportation ability "Temporal Barrier AutoBlink" Hediff while worn. If a character in your save already has this item equipped, simply unequip and re-equip it to gain the teleportation ability.

Best for:
- Players who want powerful stat boosts and a shield without sacrificing their character's unique appearance.
- Players looking for a strong endgame defensive equipment option.
- Players who need a lot of carrying capacity (e.g., using IRBM but find the reload speed too slow).
- Players who want super high defense (you can facehug bugs with this).
		
- Tweaked the accuracy of the "Bastion of Stability" and "Eternal EXARCH Turret" to better fit their status as the "ultimate ranged turrets."
(No more "outline painting" where the enemy walks away with a dusty coat while your own base is blown to smithereens.)

- Increased the fertility of "Cosmic Hydroponics Generation Omega" to 10,000, aligning it with its identity as the ultimate hydroponics basin.
This resolves the issue of growing super-crops (plants with 600-day growth cycles). You no longer need to rely on the Eco-Ark from Eternal Science.

- Added Combat Extended (CE) support for the Temporal Barrier Projector.
(Disclaimer: I don't play CE myself, but I had Gemini write the patch for me. If you encounter any issues, please provide feedback.)
- Note: I’ve heard rumors that the Stabilized Bulwark from AOTC may not function correctly in CE.

- Increased the speed of the "Miraculous Wastepack Atomizer"
While it was already fast, I felt it could be a bit faster, so I boosted its processing speed tenfold.

- Modified the "Stable Matter Gene Processor"
Increased the capacity to 10,000 and the provided Gene Complexity to 100,000, ensuring it truly feels like the ultimate gene processor.

- Added an auto-hydroponics feature, now the "Cosmic Hydroponics Generation Omega" will automatically harvest and replant crops. Just power it up, select the plant type, and it will take care of the rest.
For colonies with a large number of hydroponics basins, this feature can significantly reduce the workload and the number of colonists needed to manage them, alleviating performance issues caused by too many pawns.
It’s recommended to set the hydroponics basins to "forbidden" to prevent colonists from taking the planting job. If you need to stop the auto-growing logic, simply cut the power.
- Performance-wise, in my environment with 681 mods and 260 hydroponics basins, the TPS drop is negligible. 
Given the efficiency far surpasses manual planting, it seems that the efficiency of 50 auto-hydroponics basins is almost equivalent to 200 manually tended hydroponics basins.
And the higher the efficiency of the hydroponics basins, the greater the efficiency boost compared to manual planting.

- The auto-hydroponics feature has been extracted into a standalone mod, now available as "Fully Automatic Hydroponics" (Jeremie.Fully.Automatic.Hydroponics). https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3709212752

- 2026.03.20
- Further increased the carrying capacity of the Temporal Barrier Projector, as I found it still wasn't quite enough for venturing out.

- 2026.03.22
- Added support for animals to wear the Temporal Barrier Projector. Now animals can also benefit from wearing the projector. 
- This significantly increases the survivability of animals, especially in scenarios like the "Wind and Snow Orphan" (OAGene_Snowstorm_SnowstormStory) where you have a single protagonist and animals.
(Requires a mod framework that allows animals to wear apparel: Animal Apparel: Framework) https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=3513825850

- 2026.03.23
- Made the "B.E.H.O.L.D.E.R." and "T.E.R.M.I.N.U.S." compatible with shields when using Vanilla Weapons Expanded. https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013

- 2026.04.16
- Added the "Temporal Barrier AutoBlink" Hediff .
- Change the value of the Temporal Barrier Projector to 1 to avoid wealth explosion issues in colonies. It should now only be obtainable through Utopian Apparatus and developer mode, and should not naturally spawn on raiders (hopefully), and will only be recycled but not sold in interstellar trade.

- 2026.04.17
- Added an auto-hydroponics feature, now the "Cosmic Hydroponics Generation Omega" will automatically harvest and replant crops. Just power it up, select the plant type, and it will take care of the rest.

- 2026.04.18
- Added a toggle for the auto-hydroponics feature, allowing players to choose whether to enable it based on their needs.

- 2026.04.18
- The auto-hydroponics feature has been extracted into a standalone mod, now available as "Fully Automatic Hydroponics" (Jeremie.Fully.Automatic.Hydroponics).

Source Code: https://github.com/Lyoko-Jeremie/RimworldMods/tree/master/SNS_AOPC_TPOC_Patch

	</description>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>Ingendum.AnimalApparelFramework</li>
		<li>ri.rimimmortal.core</li>
		<li>rabiosus.autoblink</li>
		<!-- <li>-->
		<!-- 	<packageId>rabiosus.autoblink</packageId>-->
		<!-- 	<displayName>AutoBlink</displayName>-->
		<!-- 	<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/3493889625</steamWorkshopUrl>-->
		<!-- </li>-->
			 
		<!-- Ambition of the Cosmic_zh：AOTC简体中文汉化 -->
		<li>snsambitioncosmic.zh819</li>
		
		<li>Jeremie.Fully.Automatic.Hydroponics</li>
	</loadAfter>
	
	<modDependencies>
	    <li>
			<packageId>para0234.snsambitioncosmicgen4addon</packageId>
	        <displayName>AOTC: True Pinnacle of Creation[Continued]</displayName>
	        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/3379479793</steamWorkshopUrl>
	    </li>
	    <li>
			<packageId>Para0234.SNSAmbitionCosmic</packageId>
	        <displayName>Ambition of the Cosmic [Continued]</displayName>
	        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
	    </li>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
