<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>多年生杂交水稻 EBT1 (Perennial Hybrid Rice EBT1)</name>
    <author>Jeremie</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <packageId>Jeremie.HybridRiceEBT1</packageId>
    <description>
《稻田有望像果园 闪耀世界科学家首次发现水稻多年生“长寿基因” EBT1》

---

[通讯台接收信息]
标题： 稻田有望像果园：闪耀世界科学家分离出水稻多年生“长寿基因”EBT1
来源： 新夏星际通讯网，翠象10日（记者张建松、胡喆）
“时雨及芒种，四野皆插秧。”
这句古老的诗词描述了水稻传统的、一年生的生命周期。这意味着种植工必须在每一个生长季，煞费苦心地为这些作物重新播种。
如今，闪耀世界科学家在农业领域取得了重大突破，他们发现并克隆了“长寿基因”EBT1。这项基因改造技术创造出了一种多年生高产水稻品种，让种植区能够像果园一样运作 ——只需一次播种，就能为殖民地带来源源不断的持续收获。

---

[English Translation By Gemini 3.1 Pro]

[Comms Console Transmission]
Title: Rice Fields to Rival Orchards: Glitterworld Scientists Isolate Perennial "Longevity Gene" EBT1
Source: New Xia Comms Network, 10th of Aprimay (Reporters Zhang Jiansong, Hu Zhe)
"When seasonal rains grace the tilled earth, across the fields the seedlings are sown."
This ancient poetry describes the traditional, annual life cycle of the rice plant, demanding that growers painstakingly re-sow the crop every single growing season.
Today, Glitterworld scientists have achieved an agricultural breakthrough by discovering and cloning the "longevity gene" EBT1.
This genetic modification creates a perennial rice strain, allowing growing zones to function much like orchards—requiring only a single sowing for continuous, ongoing harvests.

---

这是一种多年生超级杂交水稻：
* 茂盛生长的水稻代表粮食无忧，观之心情舒畅
* 容易被动物吃掉，要小心，动物觉得它好吃
* 可以在贫瘠的土地上生长（0.2
* 超高的作物产率（产出60
* 极短的生长周期（首次只要3~5天即可收获
* 广泛的温度适应范围（可生长范围-127~95摄氏度，最佳生长温度0~58摄氏度
* 容易种植和收获（种植30工作量，收获100工作量，优化基因让工作更轻松
* 首次收获后能快速收获下一季（收割后生长进度恢复到70%，只要再等半天左右就能再次收获
* 偶尔会在野外出现
* 在水培盆中可以按照预期生长

This is a perennial hybrid rice:
* Lush growth represents food security and is pleasing to the eye.
* It is easily eaten by animals, so be cautious as they find it tasty.
* It can grow in poor soil (0.2 min need).
* It has an extremely high crop yield (producing 60).
* It has a very short growth cycle (the first harvest can be ready in just 3-5 days).
* It has a wide temperature tolerance (can grow in -127 to 95 degrees Celsius, with an optimal growth range of 0 to 58 degrees Celsius).
* It is easy to plant and harvest (planting requires 30 work units, harvesting requires 100 work units, and optimized genetics make the work easier).
* After the first harvest, it can quickly produce the next season's crop (after harvesting, growth progress resets to 70%, and it takes about half a day to be ready for the next harvest).
* It occasionally appears in the wild.
* It can grow as expected in hydroponic pots.

---

- 2026.03.22
- 为了修复红字，修改了defName。 从 Jeremie_Plant_HybridRiceEBT1 改为 Jeremie_Plant_HybridRiceEBT1g 。 如果之前存档里存在这个植物，可能会出错，铲掉应该就ok。

- 2026.03.23
- 修改温度适应范围。 可生长范围 -127~95 摄氏度。 最佳生长温度 0~58 摄氏度。 真不愧是超级水稻呀~~~~~


---

https://www.news.cn/20260320/f6adabd54d70457ba966828a9cbe6b98/c.html

</description>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>Dajian.ChiTeaditional.Expanded</li>
    </loadAfter>

    <modDependencies>
    </modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
