<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>全自动水栽培盆 FullyAutomaticHydroponics</name>
    <author>Jeremie</author>
    <supportedVersions>
		<li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Jeremie.Fully.Automatic.Hydroponics</packageId>
    <description>
## Jeremie 的 全自动水栽培盆 FullyAutomaticHydroponics 补丁。 解放小人的双手！

既然水栽培盆可以自动生长了，为什么不能自动播种和收获？现在，它来了！
众望所归的全自动水栽培盆补丁，让所有水栽培盆都不再需要人工种植和收获！

提供两个开关，分别控制自动播种和自动收获，默认都是关闭的。
打开自动播种开关后，水栽培盆会在没有植物的时候自动播种选定的植物。
打开自动收获开关后，水栽培盆会在植物成熟的时候自动收获。如果是一年生植物，收获后会自动播种；如果是多年生植物，收获后会继续生长，并等待再次成熟。
对于正在生长的莓果、树木这类多年生植物，同时开启自动播种和自动收获后，如果切换了设置的目标植物的种类，新的植物会在下一次成熟后自动收获时播种。
自动收获的产物会堆积在附近，就像正常人工收获的逻辑一样。

### 提示：

在打开自动播种和自动收获功能后，因为任务分配问题，小人可能会抢任务，所以请禁用水栽培盆，让小人不要去执行任务。
对于圈养的动物，可以把水栽培盆放在动物区域内，选择种植干草，打开自动播种并关闭自动收获，让动物自己去吃水栽培盆上的作物，达到自动喂食的效果。

### 性能：

当同时关闭自动播种和自动收获时，水栽培盆会恢复到原来的状态，且不产生任何副作用和性能影响。
当同时开启时，在我681个mod的环境下，260个 (AOTC:TPOC 的 星河水栽培三代 SNS_Hydroponics_III) 水栽培盆，TPS下降不明显。
因为效率远高于人工种植，实测50个星河水栽培三代水培盆的效率几乎相当于200个水栽培盆的人工种植效率了。且水培盆本身效率越高，相对于人工种植的效率提升越大。

---

### 兼容性：

已经使用C#来对所有继承自 Building_PlantGrower 的水栽培盆添加了这个功能了。所有继承自 Building_PlantGrower 的水栽培盆都应该能自动获得这个功能了。

可能和 种子需求 (SeedsPlease) 等等修改了种植需求的mod冲突，未测试。但我相信既然你都用上负正义mod了，肯定也不需要这个正义mod。
在使用 链接水栽培 (Linked Planters) 时，自动播种和自动收获功能不会在链接的水栽培盆之间传播，需要先选中整组水栽培盆后切换开关，但这个影响不大。

不支持 Automatic Hydroponics 自动水培舱 ， 因为他的水栽培盆实际上是一个类似发酵桶的自动工作台，而不是真正的植物生长建筑。

### 信息 :

mod 作者请参见 本mod的 for_modder.md 文档，了解如何为特定物品添加这个功能，或是阻止特定物品获得这个功能。

---

Source Code: https://github.com/Lyoko-Jeremie/RimworldMods/tree/master/FullyAutomaticHydroponics

-------

[English Translated By Gemini 3]

## Jeremie's Fully Automatic Hydroponics Patch. Free your colonists' hands!

If hydroponic basins can grow plants automatically, why shouldn't they sow and harvest automatically too? Well, now they can!
This long-awaited patch brings full automation to all hydroponic basins, eliminating the need for manual labor in planting and harvesting.

The mod provides two toggles to independently control **Auto-Sow** and **Auto-Harvest** (both are disabled by default).
* **Auto-Sow:** When enabled, the basin will automatically sow the selected plant whenever it is empty.
* **Auto-Harvest:** When enabled, the basin will automatically harvest plants once they reach maturity. For annual plants, it will re-sow immediately after; for perennials (like berries or certain trees), it will harvest the produce and allow the plant to continue growing for the next cycle.
* If you switch the target plant type while both toggles are active, the new plant will be sown automatically after the current crop reaches maturity and is harvested.
* Harvested products will pile up nearby, following the same logic as standard manual harvesting.

### Tips:

* **Task Conflicts:** After enabling Auto-Sow and Auto-Harvest, pawns might still try to "compete" for the job due to task assignment logic. It is recommended to **forbid** the hydroponic basins to ensure colonists stay away and let the mod handle it.
* **Auto-Feeder:** For livestock, you can place hydroponic basins within an animal area, set them to grow Haygrass, enable Auto-Sow, and **disable** Auto-Harvest. Animals will eat the crops directly from the basin, creating an automated feeding system.

### Performance:

* When both toggles are disabled, the hydroponic basins revert to their vanilla state with no side effects or performance impact.
* In a testing environment with 681 mods and 260 high-tier basins (SNS_Hydroponics_III from AOTC:TPOC), the impact on TPS (Ticks Per Second) was negligible.
* Because automation is far more efficient than manual labor, 50 automated high-tier basins are roughly equivalent to 200 manually tended ones. The higher the base efficiency of the basin, the greater the performance gain compared to manual labor.

---

### Compatibility:

This mod uses C# to apply functionality to all buildings inheriting from `Building_PlantGrower`. Most modded hydroponic basins should be supported automatically.

* **Conflicts:** May conflict with mods that fundamentally change planting requirements (such as *SeedsPlease*). These have not been tested. (Though if you are playing with hardcore difficulty mods, you likely wouldn't want an "OP" automation mod like this anyway!)
* **Linked Planters:** When using the *Linked Planters* mod, the auto-sow/harvest settings do not automatically propagate through the link. You will need to select the entire group of basins to toggle the settings, but this is a minor inconvenience.
* **Unsupported:** Does **not** support the mod *Automatic Hydroponics*, as those "basins" are technically structured as automated workbenches (similar to fermenting barrels) rather than actual plant-growing buildings.

### Information:

Mod authors should refer to the `for_modder.md` documentation in this mod's folder to learn how to manually add this feature to specific items or exclude specific items from receiving it.

	</description>
	<loadBefore>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
	</loadAfter>
	<modDependencies>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
