<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>全自动水栽培盆 FullyAutomaticHydroponics</name>
    <author>Jeremie</author>
    <supportedVersions>
		<li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Jeremie.Fully.Automatic.Hydroponics</packageId>
    <description>
## Jeremie 的 全自动水栽培盆 FullyAutomaticHydroponics 补丁。 解放小人的双手！

既然水栽培盆可以自动生长了，为什么不能自动播种和收获、自动放到该放的地方？现在，它来了！
众望所归的全自动水栽培盆补丁，让所有水栽培盆都不再需要人工参与！

提供三个开关，分别控制 **自动播种**  **自动收获** **自动存储** （默认均为关闭状态）：
* **自动播种：** 开启后，当水栽培盆没有植物时，会自动播种选定的植物。
* **自动收获：** 开启后，植物成熟时会自动收获。对于一年生植物，收获后会自动播种；对于多年生植物（如莓果、树木），收获后会继续生长并等待下一次成熟。
* **自动存储：** 开启后，收获的产物会自动存储在附近最适合的存储区中。如果附近没有存储区或者关闭该开关，产物将堆积在附近。
* 如果在同时开启两项功能的情况下切换了目标植物，新植物将在当前作物下一次成熟并自动收获后进行播种。

### 提示：

* **任务冲突：** 开启自动功能后，由于任务分配逻辑，小人可能会尝试“抢任务”。建议直接 **禁用（Forbid）** 水栽培盆，让小人不要去执行任务，完全由模组逻辑接管。
* **自动喂食：** 对于圈养动物，可以将水栽培盆放在动物区域内，种植干草并开启 **自动播种**、关闭 **自动收获**。动物会自动食用盆中的作物，从而实现自动喂食效果。

### 性能：

* 当同时关闭自动播种和自动收获时，水栽培盆会恢复到原生状态，不产生任何副作用或性能影响。
* 在 681 个 Mod 的复杂环境下测试，260 个高阶水培盆（AOTC:TPOC 的 SNS_Hydroponics_III）运行时的 TPS 下降并不明显。
* 由于自动化效率远高于人工：实测 50 个高阶水培盆的效率几乎等同于 200 个手工操作的水培盆。水培盆本身的生长效率越高，相对于人工种植的效率提升就越大。

* 改进的实现，当前在3472个SNS_Hydroponics_III上进行了测试，TPS可以保持在100上下，性能非常好。

---

### 兼容性：

本模组已通过 C# 对所有继承自 `Building_PlantGrower` 的类添加了此功能。绝大多数模组添加的水栽培盆都应能自动获得支持。

* **潜在冲突：** 可能与修改了种植基础需求的模组（如 *SeedsPlease* 种子需求）冲突，尚未经过测试。（不过既然你都用上增加难度的模组了，大概也不需要这种“正义”的自动化补丁）。
* **链接水栽培 (Linked Planters)：** 使用该模组时，自动化设置不会在链接的盆之间自动传播。你需要选中整组水栽培盆后统一切换开关，但这影响不大。
* **不支持：** 不支持 *Automatic Hydroponics* (自动水培舱)，因为该模组的水培盆本质上是类似发酵桶的自动工作台，而非真正的植物生长建筑。可以同时安装和使用，不互相影响。
* 可以在游戏中途添加或删除

### 信息：

Mod 作者请参阅本模组目录下的 `for_modder.md` 文档，了解如何为特定物品手动添加此功能，或阻止特定物品获得此功能。
		
		
---

Source Code: https://github.com/Lyoko-Jeremie/RimworldMods/tree/master/FullyAutomaticHydroponics

-------

[English Translated By Gemini 3]

## Jeremie's Fully Automatic Hydroponics Patch. Free your colonists' hands!

If hydroponic basins can grow plants automatically, why shouldn't they sow and harvest and store automatically too? Well, now they can!
This long-awaited patch brings full automation to all hydroponic basins, eliminating the need for manual labor in planting and harvesting.

The mod provides three toggles to independently control **Auto-Sow**, **Auto-Harvest**, and **Auto-Store** (all are disabled by default).
* **Auto-Sow:** When enabled, the basin will automatically sow the selected plant whenever it is empty.
* **Auto-Harvest:** When enabled, the basin will automatically harvest plants once they reach maturity. For annual plants, it will re-sow immediately after; for perennials (like berries or certain trees), it will harvest the produce and allow the plant to continue growing for the next cycle.
* **Auto-Store:** When enabled, harvested products will automatically be stored in the nearest suitable stockpile. If no stockpile is nearby or if this toggle is disabled, the products will pile up nearby instead.
* If you switch the target plant type while both toggles are active, the new plant will be sown automatically after the current crop reaches maturity and is harvested.

### Tips:

* **Task Conflicts:** After enabling Auto-Sow and Auto-Harvest, pawns might still try to "compete" for the job due to task assignment logic. It is recommended to **forbid** the hydroponic basins to ensure colonists stay away and let the mod handle it.
* **Auto-Feeder:** For livestock, you can place hydroponic basins within an animal area, set them to grow Haygrass, enable Auto-Sow, and **disable** Auto-Harvest. Animals will eat the crops directly from the basin, creating an automated feeding system.

### Performance:

* When both toggles are disabled, the hydroponic basins revert to their vanilla state with no side effects or performance impact.
* In a testing environment with 681 mods and 260 high-tier basins (SNS_Hydroponics_III from AOTC:TPOC), the impact on TPS (Ticks Per Second) was negligible.
* Because automation is far more efficient than manual labor, 50 automated high-tier basins are roughly equivalent to 200 manually tended ones. The higher the base efficiency of the basin, the greater the performance gain compared to manual labor.

* With the improved implementation, testing on 3472 SNS_Hydroponics_III basins showed TPS can be maintained around 100, which is very good.

---

### Compatibility:

This mod uses C# to apply functionality to all buildings inheriting from `Building_PlantGrower`. Most modded hydroponic basins should be supported automatically.

* **Conflicts:** May conflict with mods that fundamentally change planting requirements (such as *SeedsPlease*). These have not been tested. (Though if you are playing with hardcore difficulty mods, you likely wouldn't want an "OP" automation mod like this anyway!)
* **Linked Planters:** When using the *Linked Planters* mod, the auto-sow/harvest settings do not automatically propagate through the link. You will need to select the entire group of basins to toggle the settings, but this is a minor inconvenience.
* **Unsupported:** Does **not** support the mod *Automatic Hydroponics*, as those "basins" are technically structured as automated workbenches (similar to fermenting barrels) rather than actual plant-growing buildings. You can have both mods installed and they will not effect each other.
* Can be added to or removed from existing saves at any time.

### Information:

Mod authors should refer to the `for_modder.md` documentation in this mod's folder to learn how to manually add this feature to specific items or exclude specific items from receiving it.

	</description>
	<loadBefore>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
	</loadAfter>
	<modDependencies>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
